http://www.cobleskill.edu/about/privacy-policy.aspx

XCurrent StudentsFaculty & StaffAlumni & FriendsCommunityDirectoryGiving SearchAbout +LeadershipOffices & ServicesInstitute for Rural VitalityOur Mission & VisionChancellor Johnson's ThemesFacts & FiguresSustainabilityAccoladesDirections & Campus MapAcademics +Programs of StudyRegistrarStudy AbroadEducational Support ServicesProfessional & Continuing EdCollege in High SchoolLibraryAcademic Continuity PlanAdmission & Aid +First Year InfoTransfer InfoInternational InfoAccepted StudentsCost & Financial AidApplyRequest InfoVisit & ConnectCampus Life +Activities & OrganizationsHousingCAS, Inc./DiningCommuter StudentsStudent EmploymentHealth & CounselingCenter for Career DevelopmentTechnologyVeterans AffairsUniversity PoliceAthletics +Fighting Tigers WebsiteSwimming LessonsNews & Events +Press ReleasesMedia HubEvents CalendarCollege Magazine×Search×SearchCurrent StudentsFaculty & StaffAlumni & FriendsCommunityDirectoryGivingOpen SearchAboutLeadershipOffices & ServicesInstitute for Rural VitalityOur Mission & VisionChancellor Johnson's ThemesFacts & FiguresSustainabilityAccoladesDirections & Campus MapAcademicsPrograms of StudyRegistrarStudy AbroadEducational Support ServicesProfessional & Continuing EdCollege in High SchoolLibraryAcademic Continuity PlanAdmission & AidFirst Year InfoTransfer InfoInternational InfoAccepted StudentsCost & Financial AidApplyRequest InfoVisit & ConnectCampus LifeActivities & OrganizationsHousingCAS, Inc./DiningCommuter StudentsStudent EmploymentHealth & CounselingCenter for Career DevelopmentTechnologyVeterans AffairsUniversity PoliceAthleticsFighting Tigers WebsiteSwimming LessonsNews & EventsPress ReleasesMedia HubEvents CalendarCollege MagazineCOVID-19 // CARES Act Information // Daily Check-In // COVID-19 Dashboard
Home
About
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Open Section Menu
Leadership
+
Overview
Read Our SUNY-wide GDPR Privacy Notice
IntroductionConsistent with the provisions of the Internet Security and Privacy Act, the Freedom
of Information Law, and the Personal Privacy Protection Law, this policy describes
SUNY Cobleskill's privacy practices regarding information collected from users of
this website. This policy describes what information is collected and how that information
is used. Because this privacy policy only applies to this website, you should examine
the privacy policy of any website, including other state agency websites, that you
access using this website.
For purposes of this policy, "personal information" means any information concerning
a natural person which, because of name, number, symbol, mark, or other identifier,
can be used to identify that natural person. SUNY Cobleskill does not collect any
personal information about you unless you provide that information voluntarily by
sending an e-mail, responding to a survey, or completing an on-line transaction.
Information Collected Automatically When You Visit this WebsiteWhen visiting this website, SUNY Cobleskill automatically collects and stores the
following information about your visit:
User client hostname. The hostname or Internet Protocol address of the user requesting
access to a state agency website.
HTTP header, "user agent." The user agent information includes the type of browser,
its version, and the operating system on which that the browser is running.
HTTP header, "referrer." The referrer specifies the web page from which the user accessed
the current web page.
System date. The date and time of the user's request.
Full request. The exact request the user made.
Status. The status code the server returned to the user.
Content length. The content length, in bytes, of any document sent to the user.
Method. The request method used.
Universal Resource Identifier (URI). The location of a resource on the server.
Query string of the URI. Anything after the question mark in a URI.
Protocol. The transport protocol and the version used.
None of the foregoing information is deemed to constitute personal information.
The information that is collected automatically is used to improve this websites content
and to help SUNY Cobleskill understand how users are interacting with the website.
This information is collected for statistical analysis, to determine what information
is of most and least interest to our users, and to improve the utility of the material
available on the website. The information is not collected for commercial marketing
purposes and SUNY Cobleskill is not authorized to sell or otherwise disclose the information
collected from the website for commercial marketing purposes.
CookiesCookies are simple text files stored on your web browser to provide a means of distinguishing
among users of this website. The use of cookies is a standard practice among Internet
websites. To better serve you, we occasionally use "session cookies" to enhance or
customize your visit to this website. Session cookies can be created automatically
on the device you use to access this college website do not contain personal information
and do not compromise your privacy or security. We may use the cookie feature to store
a randomly generated identifying tag on the device you use to access this website.
A session cookie is erased during operation of your browser or when your browser is
closed.
The software and hardware you use to access the website allows you to refuse new cookies
or delete existing cookies. Refusing or deleting these cookies may limit your ability
to take advantage of some features of this website.
Information Collected When You E-mail this Website or Complete a TransactionDuring your visit to this website you may send an e-mail to SUNY Cobleskill. Your
e-mail address and the contents of your message will be collected. The information
collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic
information formats included in the message. Your e-mail address and the information
included in your message will be used to respond to you, to address issues you identify,
to improve this website, or to forward your message to another State agency for appropriate
action. Your e-mail address is not collected for commercial purposes and SUNY Cobleskill
is not authorized to sell or otherwise disclose your e-mail address for commercial
purposes.
During your visit to this website you may complete a transaction such as a survey,
registration, or order form. The information, including personal information, volunteered
by you in completing the transaction is used by SUNY Cobleskill to operate SUNY Cobleskill
programs, which include the provision of goods, services, and information. The information
collected by SUNY Cobleskill may be disclosed by SUNY Cobleskill for those purposes
that may be reasonably ascertained from the nature and terms of the transaction in
which the information was submitted.
SUNY Cobleskill does not knowingly collect personal information from children or create
profiles of children through this website. Users are cautioned, however, that the
collection of personal information submitted in an e-mail will be treated as though
it was submitted by an adult, and may, unless exempted from access by federal or State
law, be subject to public access. The college strongly encourages parents and teachers
to be involved in children's Internet activities and to provide guidance whenever
children are asked to provide personal information on-line.
Information and ChoiceAs noted above, SUNY Cobleskill does not collect any personal information about you
unless you provide that information voluntarily by sending an e-mail, responding to
a survey, or completing an on-line form. You may choose not to send us an e-mail,
respond to a survey, or complete an on-line form. While your choice not to participate
in these activities may limit your ability to receive specific services or products
through this website, it will not normally have an impact on your ability to take
advantage of other features of the website, including browsing or downloading information.
Disclosure of Information Collected Through This WebsiteThe collection of information through this website and the disclosure of that information
are subject to the provisions of the Internet Security and Privacy Act. SUNY Cobleskill
will only collect personal information through this website or disclose personal information
collected through this website if the user has consented to the collection or disclosure
of such personal information. The voluntary disclosure of personal information to
SUNY Cobleskill by the user, whether solicited or unsolicited, constitutes consent
to the collection and disclosure of the information by SUNY Cobleskill for the purposes
for which the user disclosed the information to SUNY Cobleskill, as was reasonably
ascertainable from the nature and terms of the disclosure.
However, SUNY Cobleskill may collect or disclose personal information without consent
if the collection or disclosure is: (1) necessary to perform the statutory duties
of SUNY Cobleskill, or necessary for SUNY Cobleskill to operate a program authorized
by law, or authorized by state or federal statute or regulation; (2) made pursuant
to a court order or by law; (3) for the purpose of validating the identity of the
user; or (4) of information to be used solely for statistical purposes that is in
a form that cannot be used to identify any particular person.
Further, the disclosure of information, including personal information, collected
through this website is subject to the provisions of the Freedom of Information Law
and the Personal Privacy Protection Law.
SUNY Cobleskill may disclose personal information to federal or state law enforcement
authorities to enforce its rights against unauthorized access or attempted unauthorized
access to SUNY Cobleskill's information technology assets.
Retention of Information Collected Through this WebsiteThe information collected through this website is retained by SUNY Cobleskill in accordance
with the records retention and disposition requirements of the New York State Arts
& Cultural Affairs Law. Information on the requirements of the Arts & Cultural Affairs
Law may be found at www.archives.nysed.gov/a/nysaservices/ns_mgr_retention_records.shtml. In general, the Internet services logs of SUNY Cobleskill, comprising electronic
files or automated logs created to monitor access and use of college services provided
through this website, are retained for 3 months and then destroyed. Information, including
personal information, that you submit in an e-mail or when you complete a survey,
registration form, or order form is retained in accordance with the records retention
and disposition schedule established for the records of the program unit to which
you submitted the information. Information concerning these records retention and
disposition schedules may be obtained through the Internet privacy policy contact
listed in this policy.
Access to and Correction of Personal Information Collected Through this WebsiteAny user may submit a request to the SUNY Cobleskill privacy compliance officer to
determine whether personal information pertaining to that user has been collected
through this website. Any such request shall be made in writing and must be accompanied
by reasonable proof of identity of the user. Reasonable proof of identity may include
verification of a signature, inclusion of an identifier generally known only to the
user, or similar appropriate identification. The address of the privacy compliance
officer is:
Caleb GrantSUNY CobleskillCobleskill, NY 12043
The privacy compliance officer shall, within five (5) business days of the receipt
of a proper request, provide access to the personal information; deny access in writing,
explaining the reasons therefore; or acknowledge the receipt of the request in writing,
stating the approximate date when the request will be granted or denied, which date
shall not be more than thirty (30) days from the date of the acknowledgment.
In the event that SUNY Cobleskill has collected personal information pertaining to
a user through the college website and that information is to be provided to the user
pursuant to the user's request, the privacy compliance officer shall inform the user
of his or her right to request that the personal information be amended or corrected
under the procedures set forth in section 95 of the Public Officers Law.
Confidentiality and Integrity of Personal Information Collected Through this WebsiteSUNY Cobleskill is strongly committed to protecting personal information collected
through this website against unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Consequently,
SUNY Cobleskill limits employee access to personal information collected through this
website to only those employees who need access to the information in the performance
of their official duties. Employees who have access to this information follow appropriate
procedures in connection with any disclosures of personal information.
In addition, SUNY Cobleskill has implemented procedures to safeguard the integrity
of its information technology assets, including, but not limited to, authentication,
monitoring, auditing, and encryption. These security procedures have been integrated
into the design, implementation, and day-to-day operations of this website as part
of our continuing commitment to the security of electronic content as well as the
electronic transmission of information.
For website security purposes and to maintain the availability of the website for
all users, the college employs software to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized
attempts to upload or change information or otherwise damage this website.
DisclaimerThe information provided in this privacy policy should not be construed as giving
business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information
provided through this website.
© SUNY Cobleskill 2018
